(All characters and organisations in this drama are fictional.)
(Filming with minors followed broadcast guidelines,)
(and generative AI was used in select scenes.)
I won't disappoint Seo Hyun anymore,
or hurt her,
or confuse her.
What do you mean by that?
It means I'm done with us just being friends.
Mu Jin!
So, you're telling me...
Not like a brother and sister, but as a man and a woman.
Let's date for real, Seo Hyun.
What do you think you're doing?
Are you toying with my Seo Hyun, or what?
- Is my daughter a pushover? - Mom!
She's not a pushover.
And I'm certainly not toying with her.
If you'll just give me a chance,
I'd like to try starting something with Seo Hyun.
I heard you were seeing someone else.
I heard the woman you couldn't forget...
for eight years came back.
What about her?
Mom!
It's over with her.
It ended eight years ago.
So?
Is my Seo Hyun just her replacement?
Mom, what is wrong with you?
It's not like that.
You don't love her. You just pity her.
You feel sorry for her,
out of guilt and a sense of responsibility.
So what if it's not love? So what if it's pity?
Who cares if it's guilt,
or if I'm just a rebound?
Seo Hyun.
I don't know what you're really thinking,
and even if you're only saying this on a whim,
I don't care.
I'm okay with it.
I'm okay with all of it.
Thank you for asking to be with me.
Thank you so much.
Mom, do you realise how strange you're being?
You're the one being strange.
Have you no self-respect?
What do you think you're lacking?
What's so wrong with you...
that you'd debase yourself for a man who doesn't even love you?
It's no better than begging.
What on earth do you think you're doing?
What does self-respect have to do with love?
If it means I can have him, what's wrong with begging a little?
I would do even more than that.
How can you say that in front of your mother...
Do you think your father and I raised you...
with such care just so you could be treated like this?
I know I may seem pathetic and foolish to you,
but this is me.
I hate this about myself, and it's despicable,
but this is who I am, Mom.
Ms. Han.
Ma'am, you're here.
Ms. Han,
you shouldn't treat Heung Sik like that.
What on earth did you say to him?
He's just whimpering and sulking, and has taken to his bed.
What was it?
My goodness, this is so frustrating. Fill me in.
Just a little while ago,
he was perfectly fine, chewing on some squid.
Then after your call, he suddenly...
collapsed like a leaf in a storm and took to his bed.
This is your fault, isn't it?
Yes, you're right. It is my fault.
So you finally went and told him.
To a boy who isn't even fully healed.
You really told him that Gyeol's Dad was back, didn't you?
No, that's not it, Ma'am.
Then what is it?
Heung Sik hasn't given me an answer yet.
When I hear his answer, I'll let you know right away, Ma'am.
Fine. I see.
So now that Gyeol's Dad is back,
you told him to stop pestering you and to stay away.
You drove a nail right through my Heung Sik's heart.
Gyeol's Dad isn't here, Ma'am.
Gyeol is my son.
My goodness. I'm starting to see your true colours.
He ended up like that trying to save your child.
How could you be so cruel to my son?
No matter how badly you wanted to or how urgent it was,
you should have waited until the cast was off Heung Sik's arm.
Does my Heung Sik need a cast for his heart now too?
Are you sick, Gyu Rim?
What's wrong with you,
going around asking just anyone out like that?
Don't you even know how scary men can be?
What's this?
A strapping young man...
who could take down a bull with his bare hands...
is lying here looking pathetic just because of a few words?
Get up right now!
Just leave me alone. I have things to think about.
Think about what?
Is Gyu Rim the only woman in the world?
Just because I'm hung up on Gyu Rim,
why are you hung up on her too?
Don't you have your own type?
Oh, come on.
A man needs confidence, even if he's dying tomorrow.
Ouch! That hurts.
How can your hands sting that much?
You may not have a decent job,
and objectively, you don't really have...
anything to show for yourself.
But to me, you're the greatest son in the world.
Bring me Chris Evans.
I would never trade you for him. Not in a million years.
That's not it, Mom.
If it's not, then snap out of it, you punk.
Stop looking so pathetic...
in front of your mother who gave birth to you!
Gyu Rim officially asked me to be with her.
Right, Gyu Rim asked you to officially...
Oh my goodness.
Goodness, now you're talking nonsense, you brat.
When that sign fell, did you hit your head too?
How many fingers am I holding up?
Gosh, three.
I'm perfectly sane.
Gyu Rim really did ask me out.
Are you sure Gyu Rim isn't sick or something?
Was Gyu Rim acting okay, Mom?
So Gyu Rim really said she wants to date you?
Yes.
Oh, dear. What should I do?
Why are you laughing one minute...
and crying the next? You're scaring me.
What am I going to do?
Oh, I had no idea.
I can't believe what I said to Gyu Rim.
Gosh, what am I going to do with this big mouth of mine?
- Oh, dear. - Why? What did you say?
Are you crazy? What did you say?
- What did you say to Gyu Rim? - I'm so embarrassed.
This is driving me crazy. Seriously, what did you say?
I don't know. What am I supposed to do?
Son, what are you doing?
If you're not busy, want to go on a date with Mom?
(Damga Charcoal Grill)
Is it good?
Yes, it's delicious.
Today,
I asked Mr. Jo Heung Sik out.
Really?
But I haven't heard his answer yet. He might turn me down.
Are you shocked?
I'm a little surprised.
But...
are you doing this because of me?
Because you're grateful that...
Mr. Jo Heung Sik saved me?
That's part of the reason.
But it's not the only reason.
Then what is it?
I don't know when it started,
but I've always felt a little cold.
But when I'm with Ms. Park Su Nam and Mr. Jo Heung Sik,
I feel so warm and happy.
It's like finding spring in a winter blizzard.
Really?
But for such wonderful people,
how could I be the one to upset them and make them cry?
I should be doing everything I can to make them happy.
I've been thinking about that.
And I also told you that I wished I had a dad.
Right, that's one of the reasons too.
I see. That makes some sense.
It does?
To be honest,
I was feeling very conflicted about it.
But now that my son understands,
it's such a relief.
So are you going to marry Mr. Jo Heung Sik too?
I don't know yet.
He could still turn me down.
No way. That will never happen.
Mr. Jo Heung Sik likes you so much.
If he says no, you tell me. I'll go have a word with him.
Hey, Seo Hyun.
You were taken aback by my mom, right?
No.
She was probably the one who was taken aback by me.
And you must have been very surprised too.
I'm not going to let you back out.
Even if you call in an hour...
and say you were just having a crazy moment...
and ask to take back your confession,
I'm not letting you back out.
- Okay. - Or if you changed your mind...
and ask me to pretend I didn't hear you,
I'm not letting you back out.
Okay.
Or if you think it over and decide...
you can't forget Han Gyu Rim and you cry and beg,
I'm still not letting you back out.
Okay.
There's no turning back now.
- Okay. - No take-backs.
There.
I just wanted to make sure. That's why I called.
See you again tomorrow.
Yes.
Okay, sleep well.
What's this?
Earthlings call this a "cake."
Is today my birthday?
Is it your birthday?
You can't even remember your own birthday or mine,
you thoughtless jerk.
Here, hold this.
To day one. Congratulations.
Blow them out. I want to take a picture.
What is this?
Are we dating now?
Because I'm really not into you.
Are you crazy? I'm not into you either.
You said you agreed to date Seo Hyun.
The candles are melting, man.
I had to beg them to sell me this last night...
as they were closing.
Oh, for goodness' sake.
You did the right thing.
You absolutely did the right thing.
A relationship doesn't have to start with a fiery passion on both sides.
Feelings can grow as you date someone.
That's enough.
You ended things well...
with Han Gyu Rim, right?
Did you end things properly with Gyu Rim?
When did I ever...
start anything with Gyu Rim?
That's true.
You never even got to start.
Anyway,
all it took was you changing your mind,
and now everyone's happy.
Is that really true?
What is?
That everyone is happy.
Is that really true?
Why do you keep laughing?
Me? When?
Just now.
- What? - Earlier, in the shower,
you were laughing out loud.
I could hear you all the way out here.
I don't think I did that.
Did I?
Do you have no pride either?
After all the heartache Mu Jin caused our Seo Hyun,
you just let it go so easily and laugh about it.
Are you really Seo Hyun's father?
Oh my.
There you go, laughing again.
I can't stand Mu Jin.
He could be the last man on Earth, and I still wouldn't approve.
Honestly, how can a man's feelings change at the drop of a hat?
How do we know when he'll change his mind again?
Goodness.
If that brat breaks Seo Hyun's heart again...
I swear, this time...
Honey.
Are you holding back a laugh?
You know, seeing you get all worked up...
and cussing someone out and getting angry...
is a first for me since we met.
So you find that funny?
So me getting all worked up and angry is funny to you?
No, it's not that it's funny.
I'm grateful. Okay?
Okay...
I find the fact that you're so upset for Seo Hyun's sake...
beautiful,
and I'm so grateful for it. You know?
What is this man talking about?
Do you know how adorable you are?
Oh, honey.
Sometimes, I feel like I'm the fake father,
and you're Seo Hyun's real mother. I do.
- What are you talking about? - What?
I am Seo Hyun's mother.
I may not have given birth to her,
but from the moment I married you, Seo Hyun has been my child.
I know. Of course, I know that.
Then why would you say that?
Getting upset and angry...
because you're worried your child will be hurt...
is only natural for a mother.
What's so beautiful or worth being grateful for about that?
What on earth do you take me for?
- How could you say that? - Honey.
No, that's not what I meant...
Oh, I'm sorry. That was thoughtless of me.
I'm truly sorry.
Oh, Yoon Hee. Yoon Hee.
Please, listen to me.
That's not what I was trying to say.
It's just...
Can I become a good father...
with your children?
Gyu Rim, Gyu Young, and Gyu Oh, right?
It's a little late,
but I want to start acting like a father to them, too.
Could you give me that chance?
Can you?
Don't scold me.
I just checked my blood pressure, and it was 160.
And putting cucumbers on your face lowers blood pressure?
There are some cucumbers left, so you should come put some on.
As for the laundry,
I'll fold it later when my blood pressure goes down.
It's fine.
Come on, I'm telling you to come take care of your skin.
Gyu Young's wedding is less than a month away.
Just give up on Gyu Young's wedding, Dad.
Her future husband's family thinks you passed away...
I'm not dead.
I have been resurrected.
After Gyu Young thought about it, she realised she needed her father.
She begged me for forgiveness.
She said she was wrong...
and pleaded with me to come to the wedding...
while shedding these big, fat tears.
Gyu Young did?
Yes. I...
It's falling off, darn it.
You know I have a real soft spot for people who need me, right?
I was going to say, "I don't have a daughter like you,"
and just completely ignore her.
But I'm still her father.
How could I do the same to her? Right?
So you should just pretend to give in...
and come with me. Okay?
Darn it.
Gyu Rim,
just be the one to give in. All right?
You're the eldest, after all.
Goodness.
You startled me.
I almost pierced my ear in the wrong place.
- Don't you know how to knock? - What is going on?
Did you tell your future husband's family the truth about Dad?
He said you asked him to come to your wedding.
As if.
Dad's the one who took a joke way too seriously.
You lied to Dad?
It wasn't a lie. It was a joke. A joke.
That's not something to joke about.
Do you have any idea how excited Dad is...
about going to your wedding?
Well, you can calm him down for me. Now, give me the earrings.
You made this mess, so you clean it up.
Give me the earrings. I have to get to work.
Fix this first, then go to work.
It's not like Dad did what I asked him to do, either.
What did you ask Dad to do?
I told him to tell Su Nam and the Rice Thief,
Jo Heung Sik, that Gyeol's Dad was back. Why?
You told him to do that?
That's right, I did. To break you and Jo Heung Sik up.
Why?
Because he keeps meddling in my affairs and threatening me...
all because of you.
So you're the one who dragged Mrs. Park into this.
- What? - Who are you, hurting good people?
If it weren't for those two,
our family wouldn't have made it this far.
What gives you the right?
What gives me the right?
Unbelievable.
Hi, it's Gyeol. Mister, how are you feeling today?
I'm feeling a whole lot better.
I'll be getting this cast off soon too.
That's a relief.
It wasn't a serious injury to begin with.
You really don't have to worry so much.
Mister, by the way,
is it true my mom asked to be with you?
Gyeol, how do you know about that?
- No way. - My mom told me.
She said she's waiting for your answer.
So, when are you going to answer her?
Will it take a long time?
How long will it take?
Well, you see... It's just...
Should I even dare to give an answer or not?
Whether I have the right to or not.
Can't you do it a little sooner?
You need to answer soon so I can make my decision soon too.
So will you accept my mom's feelings or not?
Can't you at least give me the odds?
The odds?
Hey, what are you even asking? It's a hundred to zero, obviously.
Hey, Han Gyu Oh, what are you doing?
That's my call. Put the phone to my ear!
Hey, Han Gyeol, you're so cool.
How so?
I mean, I thought if your mom got a boyfriend,
you'd tell her to break up with him immediately,
and throw a tantrum, begging her to focus only on you.
I'm so surprised by how cool and awesome you are.
I suppose I am.
(Children Who Benefit the World)
I have to get to class. Bye.
Tell Mr. Jo Heung Sik I'll call him again.
Mu Jin and Seo Hyun?
Since when?
(Chairman Hong Ok Seon)
But Yoon Hee is strongly against it.
Yoon Hee is?
Well, Mu Jin did cause Seo Hyun a lot of heartache.
But as they say, no parent can win against their child.
My gosh. You're one to talk.
After all this time you spent railroading your kids.
Chairman Jang, what about you? Are you against Mu Jin too?
Me?
Well...
Well, Seo Hyun likes him.
Whether I was annoyed with him in the past or not,
I just hope the two of them can be happy together.
I don't know.
If Yoon Hee keeps opposing it, it'll be hard for me.
Listen...
Hey, Chairman Jang, are you and Yoon Hee...
free this evening?
I was thinking we could have dinner, and I could talk to Yoon Hee.
Yes. Chairman Jang, you talk to her for me. Okay?
I'm counting on you, my friend.
(Chairman Hong Ok Seon)
Are you busy?
Is it true that Mu Jin asked Seo Hyun to date him?
He asked Seo Hyun right in front of Yoon Hee for her blessing.
What about Han Gyu Rim?
What about his son?
Be quiet.
We're not even sure if he's Mu Jin's son,
so be quiet.
Should I stop looking into it, then?
Put it on hold for now.
Nothing good will come of it if Seo Hyun's family finds out.
We can't just pour cold water on them...
when they've barely just begun.
There's no such thing as a secret in this world.
Even if they find out eventually, now is not the time.
This is the last order, right?
Yes, Chef. I've really learned a lot.
Thank you for everything, Chef.
What's with that look? You're creeping me out.
There's a customer.
We're about to go on break. What customer?
A customer for you.
You guys go ahead and eat and rest as planned.
You guys don't even wait to hear the whole thing.
Who is it?
There are no straws.
Okay.
What brings you here?
I took a taxi.
Is there something you wanted to say to me?
I have something to say, and something to ask.
Well...
To be honest,
I'm not Gyu Rim's husband.
Yes, I know that.
You know?
Did Gyu Rim tell you?
Is that important?
Well, no, that's not important.
But Gyu Rim...
asked me out yesterday.
What, did you come here to brag?
I didn't come here to brag.
It's just...
Oh, here...
Is it okay if I date Gyu Rim?
I wanted to see if there was any chance...
you and Gyu Rim might get back together.
That's what I came here to find out.
No.
That was a fast answer.
- You didn't hear it correctly. - No.
Hey, don't just keep saying no.
- I'll ask you again, slowly. - No.
Hey, don't do something you'll regret later.
I'm going to count to ten,
so think about it carefully and then answer me.
- One. - No.
There's absolutely no chance we'll get back together.
Can you really cut...
your feelings so cleanly, just like that?
So what is it you want to hear from me?
An honest answer. All right? Put your hand on your heart,
look up to the sky,
and give me an honest answer, with nothing to be ashamed of.
I've already told you no several times,
but you don't seem to be getting the message.
I'm a bit busy today.
You should go. I'll call a taxi for you.
Would you like some more?
So he's really saying no?
Please get up.
That's great. You know what?
This is a great way to relieve three days of pent-up stress.
Doesn't the owner complain that I come so often...
without even buying anything?
Not at all. You can come every day.
Manager Song, talk to Gyu Rim for me.
Tell her to put this in her father's room.
- Just mention it casually. - Okay.
Goodness.
I'm going to lose my mind. Right?
After causing such a ridiculous mess,
look at you just lying there without a care in the world.
Get up right now. You hear me? I'm about to grab you by the collar.
Hey, why would you grab my collar, ma'am?
Do you own my collar or something?
What did you tell me yesterday?
That Gyeol's Dad appeared?
And that Gyeol's Mom and my Heung Sik...
should just go their separate ways.
Did you say that or not?
What kind of grudge do you have against me...
to tell such a terrible lie?
Why do you say it's a lie?
Do you have any proof that it's a lie?
Proof? Proof...
If what you're saying is true, then why would Gyeol's Mom...
ask my Heung Sik out?
Why don't you answer that first?
Do you think my Han Gyu Rim is the kind of person...
who would two-time somebody?
Darn it.
What did you say? My Gyu Rim asked him out?
- Hey, wait. Stop this thing. - Yes, sir.
So, you're not saying she was the one who was asked out,
but that Gyu Rim asked him first?
Ma'am, are you sure you're not lying?
If you really don't believe me, go ask Gyeol's Mom yourself. Okay?
What has gotten into them lately?
Why is everyone acting so strange?
Considering all the heartache I've been through,
I really have to take it out on someone.
How should I do it?
Yes. A few months ago, you got drunk in broad daylight...
and peed on the wall over there. The neighbours...
Oh, good grief. Why are you being like this?
Seriously.
- Let go of this. - Oh my.
You seem to have too much energy, ma'am.
I have more than enough energy to take my anger out on you.
Oh, darn it.
My makeup is a mess, darn it...
I'm Han Gyu Young. My name is Han Gyu Young.
I'm Han Gyu Young.
Why are they taking so long?
When are they going to get here?
Darn it...
Darn it.
How can none of them be winners?
The great Han Gyu Young,
how did you stoop to scratching lottery tickets?
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting. I'm Kim Yoon Jin.
I need to get new business cards made.
My name is Han Gyu Young.
Han Gyu Young.
I know someone with a similar name.
Really? What's her name?
The name is similar,
but she's a completely different person from you, Gyu Young.
Oh, by the way,
you had an interesting idea.
That's why I begged them to let me meet with you.
No matter how well you do your makeup,
it oxidizes and breaks down over time, right?
That's why everyone is so obsessed with touching it up.
That's because, in the first place, the skincare...
isn't creating a proper base for the skin.
If you just get the skin's condition right,
the makeup will last longer, won't it?
Looking pretty all day long, that's the real game changer.
I like it.
I guess true geniuses are just born different.
I feel inadequate.
Let's work together.
I'll give you our full, unstinting support,
and I'll give you the best...
compensation package in the industry.
Thank you.
I'll work hard.
Please do.
Okay.
Darn it...
- Yes, Mother. - Gyu Young.
I'm not calling at a bad time, am I?
Oh, not at all. I was just taking a short break.
I should have called you first. I'm sorry, Mother.
No, it's fine.
The wedding is less than a month away,
and with the preparations and the gifts...
I was just wondering how everything was coming along.
Yes, I'm working hard to prepare everything well.
Listen, both your family and mine...
have a certain social and economic standing.
Isn't it a bit too frugal?
You know everyone is thinking that, right?
Exactly. You said it yourself, Mother,
that leaders of society must set an example.
You're absolutely right, Mother.
Oh, and I was looking at the list again,
and I noticed the fourth uncle's wife was missing.
Originally,
she and the fourth uncle were divorced, but my goodness,
they got back together two weeks ago.
Anyway, she'll be upset if we leave her out,
so let's get one more alligator bag for her.
- Is that all right? - Oh, of course. That's fine.
Gyu Young, have a wonderful day.
Yes, you too, Mother...
I'd like to cancel my instalment savings account.
Ma'am, it matures in three months.
Yes, I know that better than anyone,
and it's absolutely heartbreaking for me,
so please just cancel it.
Okay. Then as of today,
I will process the cancellation for you.
Excuse me...
I graduated from a prestigious medical school in Korea,
then immediately from a famous medical school in the US,
and I'm working as a salaried doctor...
at a dermatology clinic in Apgujeong.
By any chance,
what's the maximum for a line of credit?
One moment, please.
(Daebak Loan Capital)
(Quick Cash Specialist No-Collateral Daily and Monthly Loans)
Darn it...
(Same-Day Loans, Major Discounts Daebak Loan Capital)
No.
Once I'm married, I can pay it back in no time.
My future husband's family is a conglomerate.
A conglomerate.
Stop walking on eggshells around me, and just say what you need to say.
What could I possibly say?
If I could find a mouse hole to crawl into,
I'd want to just go and hide.
We can't have a mouse hole in a side dish shop.
We'd have to close down then.
Oh my, you're smiling at me.
Does that mean you've already forgiven me?
If I were in your shoes, Ma'am, I would've done the same thing.
You had every right to be angry.
Oh, dear.
Hey now, stop trying to be so understanding...
and just curse me out instead, okay?
Say, "You darned old hag."
Or, "You should've listened and believed me..."
"in the first place."
"Are you old and stupid or something?"
I'll do better.
I want you to be able to say,
"I'd believe Gyu Rim even if she told me pigs could fly."
I'll do so much better that you'll say that about me.
Goodness.
Honestly. You're a saint.
So how could I not fall for you?
Hey, it's past lunchtime.
Let's pull down the shutter for a bit...
and go get some ribs at the place up front, shall we?
Let's eat together when Heung Sik gets better.
Oh my.
You're already looking out for our Heung Sik like this?
I'd better not tell that boy. He'd be so touched.
What if he has a heart attack and dies on the spot?
No, no. That just won't do.
- I should stir-fry the vegetables. - Okay, you do that.
You know? I'm having a hard time keeping my mouth shut.
I feel like grabbing a bullhorn...
and announcing that Han Gyu Rim and Jo Heung Sik are dating.
I'm going to spread that rumour, you hear?
He hasn't given me an answer yet.
What? He still hasn't answered you?
He has nothing to do.
Why is he dragging his feet?
He probably needs time to think.
Think? What's there to think about?
He's just hit a once-in-a-lifetime jackpot,
and he's completely lost his mind, that boy, hasn't he?
He doesn't know how good he has it. That rotten kid.
Oh, this is just great, isn't it?
You know who I am, right?
No, I don't.
You really don't?
I said I don't know you. Who are you?
Good job. Good job, Kwon Hee Na.
What good would it do to say I know him?
You did the right thing.
Yes.
(Mrs. Park Su Nam)
- Yes, Ma'am. - Is this a good time?
I hope I'm not bothering you.
No, it's fine.
I made some side dishes that you like.
Come and get them. No, no, on second thought.
If you don't have any plans, just come to my place for dinner.
If Heung Sik were alright, I'd have him bring them to you.
What's wrong with Heung Sik?
It's nothing serious. He just got a little hurt.
I see.
I'll go visit him after work tonight.
(Kwon Hee Na)
You're going to stare a hole through your phone.
Are you waiting for a call or something?
I left a voice message, but I think I'm being ignored.
There's a girl ignoring you?
Oh, right. Thanks for helping me with this suit.
Everything went well.
Where did you go?
You don't need to know.
And I heard someone is coming to visit me tonight.
She's a nice girl your age,
so you two could be friends or something.
I'm not friends with women.
Oh, come on.
Help me get this off.
- I can't do it alone. - Oh, honestly.
- Sorry. - Take your arm out.
- Gosh. - Okay, let's get this off.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
I should buy some fruit that he likes.
Okay, over there. Yes, that's it. That's it.
Right? This one goes over there.
That's it.
- Mustard leaf kimchi. - There's more?
Gosh.
(Kim Yoon Gi)
What?
Gyu Oh, is the girl you're looking for Kwon Hee Na?
So what if she is?
Where are you now?
Okay, I know where it is. I'll be right there.
Gyu Oh, over here.
This is my friend Han Gyu Oh,
and this is my girlfriend, Suh Min Ju.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
We were just talking, and Kwon Hee Na's name came up.
Min Ju said she thinks it's someone she knows.
Gosh, this Kwon Hee Na must be really something.
I mean, usually when I call you,
you're too busy or can't be bothered,
and you're the one who never budges.
You know Kwon Hee Na?
Well...
At least catch your breath, man.
Could you possibly show me a picture?
Gyu Oh.
This isn't something weird, is it?
Of course not, honey.
She's a girl that Gyu Oh was really in love with,
and he just wants to confirm if it's her or not.
He won't be a bother at all,
and he won't put you in an awkward position.
Come on, don't you trust me?
Goodness.
Honestly.
I'm nearly 70 years old,
and who knew I'd still be feeding my 40-year-old son?
Weren't you just saying I was doing great?
Yes, I was.
That's right. You did do a good job, yes.
And thanks to that, Gyu Rim even asked you out.
What?
What? Heung Sik, someone asked you out?
No.
What do you mean, no?
Hey, he's just saying that because he's embarrassed.
Oh, right.
Hee Na, didn't you get a phone call?
Pardon? What call?
Well, from the younger brother of the woman...
who asked Heung Sik out.
He was just here helping set the table a moment ago.
Anyway,
if all goes well, he could become our in-law.
Oh, honestly, who are you trying to matchmake now?
It's not like I would give...
your number to just anybody, Hee Na.
The woman at the rice cake shop said he looks like a pretty boy.
Anyway, he's not what he looks like.
He's very thoughtful, kind, and hardworking, you know?
Honestly, right after my Heung Sik,
he's the man whose character I can vouch for the most.
I'm not interested in dating anyone right now.
No, that's not what I meant...
Gosh, have you gotten hooked on matchmaking or something?
Kids these days can handle that on their own.
You need to learn to read the room.
Read the room? What's that?
Know when to butt in and when to butt out.
You're so clueless, Mother.
When I feel like I want to date someone,
I promise I'll let you know then,
so please, you can be the one to introduce me to someone.
No, no, that's not what I meant.
Didn't you hear Hee Na say she's not interested?
Just give me more rice. With some of that dried radish.
Am I your servant?
And besides, why aren't you giving Gyu Rim an answer?
Who do you think you are? Do you think you're all that?
Do you think it's because I think I'm all that?
It's because I'm not good enough.
What's not good enough about you?
After everything I did to raise you?
- What's not good enough about you? - Please, stop twisting my words.
When did I twist your words?
I haven't twisted a thing, you brat.
Grandma, Uncle, will you two please stop?
Let's just eat, please.
Right. Let's just eat.
If you keep this up, I'm really going home.
You worthless brat.
Hey, just eat...
She's the one who asked to meet,
so what right does she have to keep us waiting?
I know.
I guess her meeting ran a little long.
She said she'd be here soon.
Honestly,
I can't stand the mom or the son.
Mr. Kim. Yes.
Can I call you back in about two hours?
Pardon?
I'm telling you, you can't do that.
I'm going to step out and take this call.
No, I told Director Park to send you an email.
Didn't you get it?
Yes.
Goodness. Where are you going? Are you going to the restroom?
No.
I'm going home.
Where did Hoon Tae go?
He went to take a call.
When he comes back,
you two can have your meal.
Wait. But...
why are you so upset?
Is it because I was a little late?
Come on. I was only 40 minutes late.
Only 40 minutes?
We're not usually this prickly with each other.
More than anyone,
you've always understood and overlooked my flaws.
And if things go well, we'll become in-laws.
Who will?
You and my family, Chairman?
Says who?
Yoon Hee.
I don't have the slightest desire to have Mu Jin as a son-in-law.
That's why I came here today.
What should I do?
What can I do to make you feel a little better...
Don't do anything.
Nothing you do will change my mind.
That girl from back then.
The one Mu Jin supposedly liked.
From that dirt-poor family,
with a widowed father,
a line of younger siblings, and just a high school diploma.
Oh, is this all because of her?
And here I was thinking...
No, he broke up with her long ago.
Eight years ago. It was a clean break.
Are you sure they really broke up?
Oh, for goodness' sake.
I mean, Mu Jin and I forgot about her long ago,
but you still remembered, Yoon Hee? Goodness.
I'm telling you, she was just a gold digger.
How would you know if she's a gold digger or not, Chairman?
Did you see her acting like one, Chairman?
Yoon Hee.
To her parents, that child must be precious and cherished too.
How can you be so reckless with your words?
If her parents heard you, it would break their hearts.
Listen here.
For someone who's supposed to be the Chairman of a company,
is this all the decency you have?
Yoon Hee,
I think you're crossing a line with me.
Right?
You're the one who has crossed the line, Chairman.
Anyway, I...
will never, ever...
approve of them dating.
Oh, honestly. My goodness, this is ridiculous.
Calm down.
Patience can prevent a murder. Calm down, now.
You're here?
Did my wife go to the restroom?
Where have you been?
Your wife went home.
What?
- Really? - That's it. I've had it.
- Why is your wife being dramatic? - About what?
Honestly, anyone would think...
she was that gold digger's mother.
What are you talking about now?
Hold on.
Oh, honestly.
Is this really your best?
Do you really think this face resembles this one?
You may not be satisfied right now,
but there's still time before the wedding.
With a proper diet and exercise, we'll get him as slim as possible.
And with some skillful cover-up makeup,
it'll be a 100 percent, no, 120 percent match.
Here, take a look. If you look here, Look.
This face transforms into this one.
Before and after.
Perfect.
- Just a moment. - Of course.
Yes, Dad.
What should I wear to your wedding?
Anything.
You have such great features...
- that you look good in anything. - I should get some skincare too.
Should I go to your clinic?
Why would someone with perfect skin like you need that?
Dad, I'm really busy right now.
I'll call you back in a little while.
Darn it.
So, shall we get back to it?
- Yes. - There's just one problem.
A problem?
This person...
is...
only 150cm tall.
Of course, we'll have him wear elevator shoes.
What?
How can you tell me something this important just now?
We can say he had a major accident right before the wedding,
and put him in a wheelchair...
You're a complete con artist, aren't you?
And you have the audacity to ask for 10,000 dollars for this?
Do you take me for a fool?
Who are you calling a con artist?
Who proposed this con in the first place?
- What? - I went out of my way...
because you're my niece's acquaintance,
found actors who fit your criteria,
and even came up with a contingency plan.
And you have the nerve to...
Forget it. Forget it. I'm not doing it.
I don't have to. This is too sleazy for me to do.
Darn it. Wait a minute.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
I was just caught off guard, and I overreacted.
Instead of putting him in a wheelchair,
let's say he's seriously injured.
We could wrap his face in bandages...
and have him lie in a bed. How about that?
We're closed for the day.
I'm here about the part-time job posting.
By any chance,
have you already filled the position?
Someone's here about the job ad.
A student?
Yes, I'm a junior in high school.
Did you bring your resume and health certificate?
Yes.
Okay.
You have a lot of experience at other restaurants.
Is this your dream career path?
No. My dream is to be a designer.
But I'll do a great job at anything you give me.
Seeing as you brought your health certificate in advance,
you must have checked the hourly wage...
and other conditions on the site.
- Yes. - What?
Oh, nothing. I was just thinking out loud.
But I like your quick response. All right then,
you can start tomorrow.
For now, you'll work weekdays from dinner service to closing.
And weekends from opening through lunch service.
What? Did I get the job?
You're not going to ask me anything else?
That's right.
We were looking for someone sharp and efficient,
and as it turns out, someone like you showed up.
So I'd say you got the job.
Yes, I think so.
I'll see you tomorrow, then. I'll work hard.
She's perfect. But of all people, why Han Gyu Min?
Han Gyu Rim.
Just when I thought I was getting away from Han Gyeol...
I mean, it's not like in all of Korea,
there's only one family with the last name Han.
I'm getting carried away.
Way too carried away.
Yes, that's good.
Okay. Just like that.
Yes, that's great.
- Okay, let's take a short break. - Okay.
- Hello, Ms. Kim. - Hi.
- Are these the new models? - Yes, that's right.
I don't think I've seen the male model before.
- Is he new? - Yes.
He's a sophomore in high school, and since he just started modelling,
he doesn't have much experience with shows or photo shoots.
But in the final round of auditions, he was the unanimous choice.
Okay, let's get back to it.
Good.
- Nice. - Yes.
He's a good pick.
- Not sure he'll be a star, but... - Good.
at least he won't be a flop.
Yes, you look great.
Okay, in for a close-up.
I'm fine. I'm not cold.
Just put it on.
It gets pretty chilly at night.
What time do you get discharged tomorrow?
Around 3 or 4 in the afternoon?
Okay.
I'll come pick you up.
Tell your parents I'm coming to get you.
No, don't come.
You'll just run into my mom again.
For now, it's best if you and my mom don't run into each other.
Okay, I understand.
No matter what my mom says, don't give up on me.
Gyu Rim. No matter what happens,
don't give up on me.
What is it?
I'm just so happy that I can't believe it.
Your button's undone.
He's my boyfriend.
This man is my boyfriend.
- Seo Hyun. - This man is my boyfriend!
This man is mine. He's my boyfriend.
What is it?
Thank you.
What is all this?
What do you think? They're gifts for my future in-laws.
You could at least offer to help if you noticed.
Actually, no. You'll just get the bags dirty.
- Don't touch them. - Where'd you get money for this?
Isn't all this incredibly expensive?
It's not stolen money, so don't worry.
Let's get a drink.
My wedding is in three weeks.
You think I want to get my dress refitted?
Fine, you don't have to drink. I'll drink alone.
I have something extremely important to talk about.
Don't even think about running off, and follow me.
Why is she being so dramatic?
You can't even drink. What's this about getting a drink?
Darn it.
Darn it. I'm an idiot for falling for this.
I'm sorry, Gyu Young.
My little sister is getting married,
and as her older sister,
I haven't been able to help at all.
I'm truly sorry.
Well, as long as you know.
Is that why you called me here?
This is so annoying, darn it.
But since I already feel bad,
I might as well go all the way.
What?
I have to...
- stop your marriage. - Hey!
The lies you told your future husband's family...
You need to come clean about everything...
- by tomorrow. - Are you crazy?
If you don't go, I will.
And how would you know where to go? How would you know who they are?
I'm sure Heung Sik knows.
You know that when I snap, I really snap, right?
And that when I do, no one can stop me.
You know that, don't you?
Hey, seriously... You're my sister.
No matter how embarrassing our family is,
how could you hire our father as a part-timer?
No.
It was my fault.
I should have stopped you back then.
He's not a part-timer.
He's a father too.
If he's Mom's husband, that makes him a father, right?
What are you talking about?
He's the man Mom remarried.
Between Mom's ex-husband and her current husband,
I chose the better father.
I didn't lie about anything.
You're so infuriating.
(Love on the Menu)
Excuse me, was anything turned in to the lost and found yesterday?
What did you lose?
I'm sure I lost something, but I don't know what it was.
Who? Han Gyu Oh?
The look in his eyes at your photo told the whole story.
Anyway, I sent Han Gyu Oh's contact info to your phone.
I refuse to give my daughter away...
to a family that tramples on people...
and acts so high and mighty like yours.
Please, just give up, Mu Jin.
No matter how hard I think, I can't remember.
Did you find what you lost?